Andrew Olsen

635 S Main St. Bountiful, Ut. 84010

(801) - 935-0295

Andyolsen1295@gmail.com

About Me

Currently employed as an Aggregate Quality Control Supervisor with 3+ years of experience in a leadership role, with over 6 years of Quality Control experience. I am passionate about Software Development and learning how the web works.

EDUCATION —

Hunter High School, West Valley City, Utah.

University of Utah Full-Stack Software Development Bootcamp, Salt Lake City, Utah.

EXPERIENCE

January 2013 – December 2014 Busser • The Old Spaghetti Factory

December 2014 – December 2016
Missionary • The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter Day Saints

March 2017 - Current Aggregate Quality Control Technician • Supervisor • Staker Parson Companies.

Additional Certification -

UDOT WAQTC Certification.

University of Utah Full-Stack Web Development Bootcamp Certification

Duties

The Old Spaghetti Factory

- Cleaned and prepared tables for new customers in a thorough and timely manner.
- Keep customers happy and satisfied.
- Keep the workstation clean.
- Ensure the restaurant was clean at the end of each night.

Staker Parson Companies

- Collecting samples and email results in a safe, efficient, and accurate manner.
- Keep the laboratory clean.
- Work with superintendents at all pits to ensure they are making the highest quality product possible.
- Certify material to be used in UDOT certified Concrete and Asphalt mix designs.
- Sample material with other agencies on jobsites to ensure results are correct.
- Send material submittals to customers for Engineer approval on jobs.

LEADERSHIP

The Old Spaghetti Factory

- Trainer for new employees.
- Closer busser. Checked off other bussers sections before they went home. Worked with managers to make sure my own sections, and the restaurant, was clean before clocking out.

The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter Day Saints

- Trainer for new missionaries.
- District Leader: Prepared and lead weekly meetings for 8-10 missionaries. Set new weekly goals and follow up on goals.
- Zone Leader: Prepared and lead monthly meetings for 16-20 missionaries. Set new monthly goals and followed up on goals.

Staker Parson Companies

- Trainer for new employees.
- Supervisor over three Quality Control labs, covering 14 different gravel pits and quarries. Participated in bi-weekly meetings with all superintendents and managers over the pits, quarries, Asphalt and Concrete departments to go over the sample results, and to set expectations for the following weeks.

REFERENCES

[Available upon request.]